<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on home/kyle</title>
    <link>/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on home/kyle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Minutes of ADHD</title>
      <link>/adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adhd/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, November 24, 2020 10:18am ADHD was a title given to me at a young age.
I guess its rather accurate given the nature of my attention span being shorter than a goldfish with Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s.
I should clean my room at some point.
I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be working, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like it right now. Or rather, i&amp;rsquo;ve tried for the past hour but my mind isn&amp;rsquo;t in agreeance.
i wonder what would happen if I just wrote out my thoughts as they came?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifts, Work, Vices, Hurt</title>
      <link>/vices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vices/</guid>
      <description>How do you know when an activity is good or bad for you? Sometimes your brain lies and says it is good but then you regret it after. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s something hard now but pays off long-term. How do you know if you should suck it up and endure the hardship now to receive the payoff later? What if you&amp;rsquo;re just abusing yourself and you don&amp;rsquo;t realize there is no long-term payoff?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diary to 1970</title>
      <link>/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/diary/</guid>
      <description>2020 September. The 9th day.
6 months after &amp;ldquo;the virus&amp;rdquo;. The meager remains of humanities reign coats a barren wasteland known as earth.
Big brother has told us to remain indoors. Unemployment is higher than the great depression. I shelter in a 7.5x7.8ft room that costs more than your college tuition, every month. I spend my day in neo-San Francisco writing codes on a personal mainframe computer that fits on my lap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Hackathon 1 -- Subtle Study</title>
      <link>/subtle-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/subtle-study/</guid>
      <description>While studying mandarin I found it tedious reading study cards 30+ minutes/day.
I browse the internet for 4+ hours a day.
Why can&amp;rsquo;t I learn mandarin while I browse the internet?
Now you can!
Introducing Subtle Study!
  Install the plugin
  Each day, new words will slowly, seamlessly be translated into mandarin.
Day 1: All english text. :(
Day 2: The word Cat is replaced with mandarin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Year Review</title>
      <link>/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/</guid>
      <description>2019 was the most crazy year of my life. I wrote 3 drafts totaling &amp;gt;10000 words trying to summarize it, but my perspective kept changing and so I felt any such summary I wrote didn&amp;rsquo;t capture how I felt. Instead I&amp;rsquo;m just publishing shortform what went down as objectively as possible.
January:
  the good: got into the 6 uni classes I wanted. Super amped!
  the growth: split with gf of ~3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>